<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science Fairytale Website</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:37:23 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:37:23 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fairytale Example</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-fairytale&quot;&gt;First Fairytale&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how you would go about creating a fairytale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-1-github&quot;&gt;Step 1: Github&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Github is a place where anybody can store projects that they are working on. Mostly this is code but it could be anything you want. It lets you save your files and store them somewhere else in case you want to work from elsewhere or something happense to your computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to make an account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-2-start-writing&quot;&gt;Step 2: Start writing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website already exists so once you have permissions to work on it, you can get going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is possible to work directly through Firefox/Chrome on the project although a little dodgy so we will have to come up with some way to test that the website isn’t broken before a new page is pushed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/science_fairytale.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Science Fairytale&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-3-enjoy&quot;&gt;Step 3: Enjoy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is really easy to add pictures and organise them :)&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2019/06/12/fairtyale-example.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2019/06/12/fairtyale-example.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We can use this to make a website!</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-would-be-perfect-for-all-our-website-ideas&quot;&gt;This would be perfect for all our website ideas!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a tool called Jekyll which builds the website HTML using a language called Markdown.
Markdown is quite easy to use, you can basically just type it up and add a few special characters to make &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt; characters and &lt;em&gt;itallic&lt;/em&gt; characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This would make it really easy to write up about our fairytales!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have any images yet but it is also really easy to include them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole thing is hosted on Github Pages and you are allowed one page entirely for free per account!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 21:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2019/06/11/notification-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2019/06/11/notification-post.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
